<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PahktheCah</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="ToLocationGrid">Change Location</string>
    <string name="ToLocationTypeMenu">Change Tour</string>
    <string name="ToLogOutScreen">Log Out</string>
    <string name="CancelAction">Cancel</string>
    <string name="to_map_button">Take Me There!</string>
    <string name="McGanns">McGann’s is one of the Boston’s most historic Irish Pubs straight from Doolin, Ireland.</string>
    <string name="mfa">The Museum of Fine Arts is one of the most comprehensive art museums in the world with the collection encompassing nearly 450000 works of arts. </string>
    <string name="oldnorthchurch">On the steeple of Old North Church, Boston’s oldest Church building, Robert Newman signaled with lanterns the approach of the British regulars. The steeple was the tallest steeple in Boston and the bells within were the first ever brought to America.</string>
    <string name="operahouse">The Boston Opera House hosts the region’s most active program of top touring Broadway shows, Boston Ballet performances and other high-quality cultural presentations and concerts in New England’s most magnificent theater. </string>
    <string name="reverehouse">The oldest building in downtown Boston, the Paul Revere House served as the home of its namesake and his family. Paul Revere is famous for his “midnight ride” to inform patriots that the British were coming to arrest them.</string>
    <string name="sciencemuseum">Along with over 700 interactive exhibits, the Museum of Science features a number of live presentations throughout the building every day, along with shows at the Charles Hayden Planetarium and the Mugar Omni Theater, the only domed IMAX screen in New England. </string>
    <string name="symphonyhall">Now in its 134th season, the Boston Symphony Orchestra gave its inaugural concert in 1881. Experienced members of the Boston Symphony unfold the history of the Orchestra-its musicians, conductors, and supporters-as well as offer information about the Hall in behind-the-scenes tours. </string>
    <string name="tdgarden">Since its grand opening in 1995, more than 30 million people have come to the TD Garden to see the arena’s famous tenants, the NHL’s Boston Bruins and NBA’s Boston Celtics. Home to approximately 200 public events annually, the TD Garden hosts well over 3.5 million people each year! </string>
    <string name="trinitychurch">Housed in a grand and historic building consistently ranked as one of America’s most significant architectural landmarks, the Trinity Church houses a thriving Christian community in the heart of Boston’s Back Bay. </string>







</resources>
